<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<SiteText>
  <Pages>
    <Register>
      <ErrorMessages>
        <UsernameTooShort>Your username needs to be longer than 6 characters.</UsernameTooShort>
        <UsernameTooLong>Your username needs to be less than 32 characters long.</UsernameTooLong>
        <UsernameInvalidCharacters>Your username contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</UsernameInvalidCharacters>
        <NullUsername>You need to enter a username.</NullUsername>
        <UsernameTaken>That username is already in use. Please choose another.</UsernameTaken>
        <InvalidEmail>Your email address needs to match the pattern \"joe@joesmith.com\".</InvalidEmail>
        <EmailTooLong>Your email needs to be less than 64 characters long.</EmailTooLong>
        <EmailTooShort>Your email needs to be longer than 6 characters.</EmailTooShort>
        <NullEmail>You need to enter an email address.</NullEmail>
        <EmailInvalidCharacters>Your email contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</EmailInvalidCharacters>
        <NullPassword>You need to enter a password.</NullPassword>
        <PasswordTooShort>Your password needs to be longer than 6 characters long.</PasswordTooShort>
        <PasswordTooLong>Your password needs to be less than 32 characters long.</PasswordTooLong>
        <PasswordInvalidCharacters>Your password contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</PasswordInvalidCharacters>
        <NullConfirmPassword>You need to provide a confirmation password.</NullConfirmPassword>
        <ConfirmPasswordMatch>Your confirm password needs to match your regular password.</ConfirmPasswordMatch>
        <ConfirmPasswordTooShort>Your confirm password needs to be longer than 6 characters.</ConfirmPasswordTooShort>
        <ConfirmPasswordTooLong>Your confirmation password needs to be less than 32 characters long.</ConfirmPasswordTooLong>
        <ConfirmPasswordInvalidCharacters>Your confirmation password contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</ConfirmPasswordInvalidCharacters>
        <AgreeToTerms>You need to agree to the terms and conditions and the privacy policy.</AgreeToTerms>        
      </ErrorMessages>
    </Register>
  </Pages>
</SiteText>