<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<SiteText>
  <Pages>
    <Signup>
      <ErrorMessages>
        <NullFirstName>You need to enter a first name.</NullFirstName>
        <FirstNameTooLong>Your first name needs to be less than 64 characters long.</FirstNameTooLong>
        <FirstNameInvalidCharacters>Your first name contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</FirstNameInvalidCharacters>
        <NullLastName>You need to enter a last name.</NullLastName>
        <LastNameTooLong>Your last name needs to be less than 64 characters long.</LastNameTooLong>
        <LastNameInvalidCharacters>Your last name contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</LastNameInvalidCharacters>
        <NullPhoneNumber>You need to enter a phone number.</NullPhoneNumber>
        <InvalidPhoneNumber>Your phone number is invalid. It needs to follow the format \"555 555-5555\".</InvalidPhoneNumber>
        <PhoneNumberTooLong>Your phone number must contain less than 20 characters.</PhoneNumberTooLong>
        <PhoneNumberInvalidCharacters>Your phone number contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, ;, or any alphabetic characters.</PhoneNumberInvalidCharacters>
        <NullBusinessName>You need to enter a business name.</NullBusinessName>
        <BusinessNameTooLong>Your business name needs to be less than 64 characters long.</BusinessNameTooLong>
        <BusinessNameInvalidCharacters>Your business name contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</BusinessNameInvalidCharacters>
        <NullDescription>You need to enter a description for your business.</NullDescription>
        <DescriptionTooLong>Your description needs to be under 200 characters long.</DescriptionTooLong>
        <DescriptionTooShort>Your description needs to be at least 10 characters long.</DescriptionTooShort>
        <DescriptionInvalidCharacters>Your description contains invalid characters. Please ensureit does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</DescriptionInvalidCharacters>
        <DescriptionOneWord>Your description needs to be more than one word.</DescriptionOneWord>
      </ErrorMessages>
    </Signup>
  </Pages>
</SiteText>