<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<EmailText>
  <ContactTextPrefix>Please contact us at</ContactTextPrefix>
  <ContactEmail>teamc4g@coupons4giving.ca</ContactEmail>
  <ContactTextSuffix>with any questions!</ContactTextSuffix>
  <UserSignup>
    <Title>Welcome To Coupons4Giving</Title>
    <Subject>Welcome to Coupons4Giving!</Subject>
    <UserContent>Thanks for registering with Coupons4Giving. Once you login to your account you can start supporting your favorite causes and purchasing great deals from a wide range of merchants and E-tailers (online only merchants).</UserContent>
    <NPOContent>Thanks for registering with Coupons4Giving. Once you login to your account you can get started. You can set up a campaign and start fundraising, and you can support your favorite causes by purchasing great deals from a wide range of Merchants and E-Tailers (online-only merchants).</NPOContent>
    <MerchantContent>Thanks for registering with Coupons4Giving. Once you login to your account you can get started. You can set up merchant offers to support your favourite Not-For-Profits, and you can support your favorite causes by purchasing great deals from a wide range of Merchants and E-Tailers (online-only merchants).</MerchantContent>
    <LinkContent>Click here</LinkContent>
    <LinkURL>https://www.coupons4giving.ca/Account/Login.aspx</LinkURL>
    <LinkSuffix>to go to your account.</LinkSuffix>
  </UserSignup>
  <OfferCreation>
    <TitlePrefix>Your New Offer on Coupons4Giving</TitlePrefix>
    <Subject>Your new Offer on Coupons4Giving</Subject>
    <ContentPrefix>Your new offer, </ContentPrefix>
    <ContentSuffix>has been set up.</ContentSuffix>
    <LinkContent>Click here</LinkContent>
    <LinkSuffix>to view your deal.</LinkSuffix>
  </OfferCreation>
  <MerchantSignup>
    <TitlePrefix>Your New Account on Coupons4Giving</TitlePrefix>
    <Subject>Your new Account on Coupons4Giving</Subject>
    <Content>Congratulations! You have just set up your Coupons4Giving Profile page. Now you can get started and set up your offers. A team member will be in touch with you shortly with some tips on how to get started. In the meantime, if you have any questions, please contact us at </Content>
    <Content2>Your unique Coupons4Giving company profile page is</Content2>
    <LinkContent>Click here</LinkContent>
    <LinkSuffix>to set up an offer.</LinkSuffix>
  </MerchantSignup>
  <NPOSignup>
    <TitlePrefix>Your New Account on Coupons4Giving</TitlePrefix>
    <Subject>Your new Account on Coupons4Giving</Subject>
    <Content>Congratulations! You have just set up your Coupons4Giving Profile page. Now you can get started and set up your campaigns. A team member will be in touch with you shortly with some tips on how to get started. In the meantime, if you have any questions, please contact us at </Content>
    <Content2>Your unique Coupons4Giving profile page is</Content2>
    <LinkContent>Click here</LinkContent>
    <LinkSuffix>to set up a campaign.</LinkSuffix>
  </NPOSignup>
</EmailText>