<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<SiteText>
  <Pages>
    <New>
      <ErrorMessages>
        <NullOfferName>You need to enter a name for your offer.</NullOfferName>
        <OfferNameTooShort>Your offer name is too short. Offer names need to be at least 5 characters long.</OfferNameTooShort>
        <OfferNameTooLong>Your offer name is too long. Offer names need to be less than 50 characters long.</OfferNameTooLong>
        <OfferNameInvalidCharacters>Your offer name contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</OfferNameInvalidCharacters>
        <OfferNameTaken>Sorry, but you already have an offer with that name. Offer names need to be unique. Please enter a different name.</OfferNameTaken>
        <NullDescription>You need to enter a description for your offer.</NullDescription>
        <DescriptionOneWord>Your offer description needs to be more than one word.</DescriptionOneWord>
        <DescriptionTooLong>Your offer description is too long. Offer descriptions need to be less than 200 characters long.</DescriptionTooLong>
        <DescriptionTooShort>Your offer description is too short. Offers descriptions need to be at least 10 characters long.</DescriptionTooShort>
        <DescriptionInvalidCharacters>Your offer description contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</DescriptionInvalidCharacters>
        <StartDateLaterThanEndDate>The start date of your offer needs to be before its end date.</StartDateLaterThanEndDate>
        <EndDateEarlierThanStartDate>The end date of your offer needs to be after its start date.</EndDateEarlierThanStartDate>
        <EndDateBeforeToday>The end date of your offer needs to be later than today&apos;s date.</EndDateBeforeToday>
        <NullAbsoluteCouponLimit>You need to enter an absolute limit for your offer. This is how many coupons you wish to sell overall.</NullAbsoluteCouponLimit>
        <CouponLimitNAN>Your absolute coupon limit needs to be a number. For example, 2500.</CouponLimitNAN>
        <CouponLimitLT0>Your absolute coupon limit needs to be greater than 0.</CouponLimitLT0>
        <CouponLimitLessThanCustomerLimit>The absolute limit of coupons to sell must be greater than or equal to the limit per customer.</CouponLimitLessThanCustomerLimit>
        <NullPCCouponLimit>You need to enter a limit per customer for your offer. This is how many coupons each individual customer is allowed to buy.</NullPCCouponLimit>
        <PCCouponLimitNAN>Your coupon limit per customer needs to be a number. For example, 2500.</PCCouponLimitNAN>
        <PCCouponLimitLT0>Your coupon limit per customer needs to be greater than 0.</PCCouponLimitLT0>
        <PCCouponLimitGreaterThanAbsoluteLimit>The limit of coupons per customer must be less than than or equal to the absolute limit of coupons to sell.</PCCouponLimitGreaterThanAbsoluteLimit>
        <NullRetailValue>You need to enter a retail value for your offer. This is how much your product or service typically costs.</NullRetailValue>
        <RetailValueNAN>Your retail value needs to be a number. For example, 25.00.</RetailValueNAN>
        <RetailValueLT1>Your retail value needs to be greater than $1.00.</RetailValueLT1>
        <RetailValueLessThanGiftValue>The retail value of your offer must be greater than than its gift value.</RetailValueLessThanGiftValue>
        <NullGiftValue>You need to enter a gift value for your offer. This is how much you this coupon will cost to purchase.</NullGiftValue>
        <GiftValueNAN>Your gift value needs to be a number. For example, 25.00.</GiftValueNAN>
        <GiftValueLT1>Your gift value needs to be greater than $1.00.</GiftValueLT1>
        <GiftValueGreaterThanRetailValue>The gift value of your offer must be less than than its retail value.</GiftValueGreaterThanRetailValue>
        <RedeemDetailsTooLong>Your additional redeem details need to be less than 500 characters long.</RedeemDetailsTooLong>
        <RedeemDetailsInvalidCharacters>Your additional redeem details contains invalid characters. Please ensure it does not contain any of the following: &lt;, &gt;, {, }, or ;.</RedeemDetailsInvalidCharacters>
        <ImageTypeInvalid>The file you uploaded is an incorrect file type. Supported types include: GIF, JPEG, Progressive JPEG, PNG, and SVG. Please select another file.</ImageTypeInvalid>
        <ImageSizeInvalid>The image you uploaded appears to be too large. We require images to be x pixels wide by y pixels high in order to display properly. Please select another image.</ImageSizeInvalid>
        <UploadError>There was a problem uploading your image. Please try again.</UploadError>
        <ServerError>Something went wrong with your form submission. Please try again.</ServerError>
        <FormErrors>There were some errors with your form submission. Please review the following errors and try again.</FormErrors>
      </ErrorMessages>
    </New>
  </Pages>
</SiteText>